NLRB vs. International Union of Operating Engineers Local 450 Court Documents 5355
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NLRB vs. International Union of Operating Engineers Local 450 Court Documents
1959
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Labor Relations Board (NLRB)
Ross, Philip
5355
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Files pertaining to the case of the United States National Labor Relations Board vs. International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 450.
5619962
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 18, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of documents pertaining to the case of the United States National Labor Relations Board vs. International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 450. The documents are from the case before the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Fifth Circuit.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Steam engineers -- Labor unions -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Labor laws and legislation -- United States; Ross, Philip; United States. National Labor Relations Board; International Union of Operating Engineers. Local 450
5619962
- Transcript of Record, Volume I, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  No. 17,789
- Brief for the National Labor Relations Board, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Appendix to Petitioner's Brief, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Brief for respondent, Local 450, International Union of Operating Engineers, AFL-CIO, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Transcript of Record, Volume I, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  No. 17,800
- Brief for Respondent, Local 450, International Union of Operating Engineers, AFL-CIO, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Appendix to Petitioner's Brief, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Brief for the National Labor Relations Board, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Transcript of Record, Volume I, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  No. 17,840
- Brief for the National Labor Relations Board, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Appendix to petitioner's brief, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Brief for respondent, Local 450, International Union of Operating Engineers, AFL-CIO, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)